//письмо тестовое
[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "вопрос",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "вопрос",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "вопрос",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "1"
  }
]
//тест простой тема 3
[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Kalem",
    "answers": [
      "Kalemler",
      "Kalemlar"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Kalemler"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Ev",
    "answers": [
      "Evler",
      "Evlar"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Evler"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Anne",
    "answers": [
      "Annelar",
      "Anneler"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Anneler"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Masa",
    "answers": [
      "Masalar",
      "Masaler"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Masalar"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Erkek",
    "answers": [
      "Erkekler",
      "Erkeklar"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Erkekler"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Gulun",
    "answers": [
      "Gulunler",
      "Gulunlar"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Gulunlar"
  }
]




//тест 1
[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Kitap (a) ->",
    "answers": [
      "Kitapa",
      "Kitaba",
      "Kitabe"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Kitaba"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Ağaç (ı) ->",
    "answers": [
      "Ağacı",
      "Ağaci",
      "Ağace"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Ağacı"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Ekmek (e) ->",
    "answers": [
      "Ekmeğe",
      "Ekmeği",
      "Ekmeki"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Ekmeğe"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Tat (ı) ->",
    "answers": [
      "Tadi",
      "Tatı",
      "Tadı"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Tadı"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Denk (i) ->",
    "answers": [
      "Denge",
      "Denki",
      "Dengi"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Dengi"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Kulak (ı) ->",
    "answers": [
      "Kulaği",
      "Kulağı",
      "Kulaki"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "Kulağı"
  }
]
//тест2
[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Ben avukat",
    "answers": [
      "avukatsın",
      "avukatsın",
      "avukatsın"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "avukatsın"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Biz doktor",
    "answers": [
      "doktor",
      "doktoruz",
      "doktorsunuz"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "doktoruz"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "O evli",
    "answers": [
      "evliyiz",
      "evliyiz",
      "evli"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "evli"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Onlar doktor",
    "answers": [
      "doktorsunuz",
      "doktorlar",
      "doktorsun"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "doktorlar"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Ben hasta",
    "answers": [
      "hastayım",
      "hastasın",
      "hastasınız"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "hastayım"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Siz mühendis",
    "answers": [
      "mühendissin",
      "mühendissen",
      "mühendissiniz"
    ],
    "questionAnswer": "mühendissiniz"
  }
]
